A Finding Aid to the Cranmer Art Group Records, circa 1980-2021, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Client Files, 1980-2021; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 55.2 Linear feet Boxes 1-54, 75
  - Client Files, 1996-1997, Paula Cooper Gallery (Yayoi Kusama), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12-13)
  - Client Files, 1996, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 1996, Willem de Kooning, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 15-16)
  - Client Files, 1996, Dia Center for the Arts (Hanne Darboven), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 1996, E-F, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 1996, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19-20)
  - Client Files, 1996, Gallery of Living Artists (Roy Newell), 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 1996, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22-23)
  - Client Files, 1996, Ikkan Art International, Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 1996, J, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 1996, Donald Judd Estate (Frank Stella), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 1996, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 1996, Nancy and Rob Keay, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Client Files, 1996, Estate of Oscar Kolin, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Client Files, 1996, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Client Files, 1996, Julian Lethbridge and Paula Cooper Gallery, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Client Files, 1996, Locksley-Shea Gallery, 1992-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Client Files, 1996, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Client Files, 1996, Brice Marden and Plance Image, Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 1996, Matthew Marks Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 1996, Maxson Young Associates (Emma Amos), 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
  - Client Files, 1996, N, Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
  - Client Files, 1996, O, Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 1996, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8-9)
  - Client Files, 1995-1996, Paine Webber, Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
  - Client Files, 1996, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 1996, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13-15)
  - Client Files, 1996-1997, Richard Serra, Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 1996, Barbara Slifka, Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 17-18)
  - Client Files, 1996, Amy Sullivan, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 1996, T-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 1996, Christopher Wool, Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 1997, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 1997, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 23-24)
  - Client Files, 1997, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 25-27)
  - Client Files, 1997, Christie's and Shea Estate, Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Client Files, 1997, D-E, Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Client Files, 1997, Dedalus Foundation, Inc., 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 1997, Willem de Kooning, Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 2-3)
  - Client Files, 1997, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 4-6)
  - Client Files, 1997, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
  - Client Files, 1997, Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum (Robert Rauschenberg, "Barge"), Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 1997, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 10-11)
  - Client Files, 1997, I-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 1997, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 13-14)
  - Client Files, 1997, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
  - Client Files, 1997, Stuart Levy (Mark Rothko), Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 1997, Sol LeWitt, Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 1997, Locksley Shea Gallery, 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 19-20)
  - Client Files, 1997, M, 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 21-24)
  - Client Files, 1997, Fair Alice McCormick and Fleur Weymouth, Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 1997, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 1997, Annalee Newman (Barnett Newman), Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 27-28)
  - Client Files, 1997, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 29-30)
  - Client Files, 1997, Valentina Pero (Robert Rauschenberg, "Pantomime"), Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Client Files, 1997, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 1997, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2-4)
  - Client Files, 1997, T-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 1997, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 1997, Fleur Weymouth, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 1997, Whitney Museum of American Art (Keith Haring), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
  - Client Files, 1998, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 10-11)
  - Client Files, 1998, American Express Co., 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 1998, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 13-16)
  - Client Files, 1998, Annibale Berlingieri (Brice Marden), 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 1998, Marianne Boesky Gallery (Gerhard Richter), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 1998, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 19-20)
  - Client Files, 1998, Paula Cooper Gallery (Yayoi Kusama), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 1998, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 22-23)
  - Client Files, 1998, Willem de Kooning, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 24-27)
  - Client Files, 1998, Willem de Kooning ("Untitled #01456"), 1998, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Client Files, 1998, The Drawing Center and Willem de Kooning, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Client Files, 1998, E, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Client Files, 1998, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 31-32)
  - Client Files, 1998, Ronald Feldman Fine Arts (Ida Applebroog), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 1998, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 1998, Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum (Robert Rauschenberg), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 1998, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 1998, I-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 1998, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
  - Client Files, 1998, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 1998, Rhoda Landis, Nordstern, and Smith Adjusters International, 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 1998, Vera Lutter, 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 1998, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Client Files, 1998, Matthew Marks Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 12-13)
  - Client Files, 1998, Matthew Marks Gallery (Peter Cain), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 14-15)
  - Client Files, 1998, Dr. and Mrs. Robert Morris, Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 1998, N, Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 17-18)
  - Client Files, 1998, O, Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 1998, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 1998, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 21-22)
  - Client Files, 1998, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 23-24)
  - Client Files, 1998, Staff Stiftung (Man Ray), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 1998, Studio Sofield Inc., 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 1998, William Shanahan, 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 27-28)
  - Client Files, 1998, T, 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 29-30)
  - Client Files, 1998, V, Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 1998, W-Y, Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 2-3)
  - Client Files, 1999, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 4-5)
  - Client Files, 1999, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
  - Client Files, 1999, The British Council (Sean Scully), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
  - Client Files, 1999, Cynthia Bing, Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 1999, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 11-13)
  - Client Files, 1999, C & M Arts (Brice Marden), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 1999, Paula Cooper Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 1999, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 1999, Dedalus Foundation, Inc. (Robert Motherwell), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 17-18)
  - Client Files, 1999, Willem de Kooning, Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 19-21)
  - Client Files, 1999, Peter Dolle, Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 1999, E, Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 1999, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 24-25)
  - Client Files, 1999, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 1999, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 27-28)
  - Client Files, 1999, I-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 1999, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
  - Client Files, 1999, Knoedler and Company (Milton Avery), Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 1999, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 5-7)
  - Client Files, 1999, Locksley Shea (Donald Judd), Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 1999, Locksley Shea (Brice Marden, "Number"), 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 1999, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 10-12)
  - Client Files, 1999, Matthew Marks Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 13-14)
  - Client Files, 1999, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 1999, Neuberger and Berman, LLC, Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 16-17)
  - Client Files, 1999, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 18-20)
  - Client Files, 1999, Plane Image, Inc. and Brice Marden, Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 1999, Q-R, Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 22-23)
  - Client Files, 1999, Robert Rauschenberg and Untitled Press, Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 1999, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 25-28)
  - Client Files, 1999, Estate of Saul Steinberg, Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Client Files, 1999, T-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Client Files, 1999, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
  - Client Files, 1999, Weatherspoon Art Gallery (Willem de Kooning), Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 1999, Weatherspoon Art Gallery (Matsumi Kanemitsu), Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 1999, Weatherspoon Art Gallery (Robert Rauschenberg), Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 1999, Y-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 2000, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 7-8)
  - Client Files, 2000, Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Brice Marden), Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 2000, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 10-11)
  - Client Files, 2000, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 12-14)
  - Client Files, 2000, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2000, Dedalus Foundation, Inc. (Robert Motherwell), Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 16-17)
  - Client Files, 2000, Willem de Kooning, Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 18-20)
  - Client Files, 2000, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 21-22)
  - Client Files, 2000, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 23-24)
  - Client Files, 2000, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 25-26)
  - Client Files, 2000, J, Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 2000, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 28-29)
  - Client Files, 2000, Knoedler and Company, Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Client Files, 2000, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Client Files, 2000, Locksley Shea (Donald Judd), 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Client Files, 2000, Irving Ludmer (Jean Dubuffet), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2000, Luhring Augustine Gallery (Christopher Wool), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 2000, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 3-4)
  - Client Files, 2000, Matthew Marks Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2000, Marlborough Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 2000-2003, Anthony Munk (Willem de Kooning, "Greece on Eighth Avenue"), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 7-8)
  - Client Files, 2000, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 9-10)
  - Client Files, 2000, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Client Files, 2000, Joann and Gifford Phillips, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 2000, Plane Image, Inc. and Brice Marden, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Includes 1 undeveloped film roll.
  - Client Files, 2000, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 14-15)
  - Client Files, 2000, Robert Rauschenberg, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2000, Michael Rosenfeld Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2000, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 18-20)
  - Client Files, 2000, Richard Serra, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2000, Phil Sims, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 2000, Sotheby's (Brice Marden), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 2000, T-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 24-25)
  - Client Files, 2000, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 26-27)
  - Client Files, 2000, Y-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Client Files, 2001, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 29-30)
  - Client Files, 2001, Ida Applebroog, Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Client Files, 2001, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
  - Client Files, 2001, Theodore and Ruth Baum, Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 4-6)
  - Client Files, 2001, Suzann Boettger and David Dorfman, Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 2001, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 8-9)
  - Client Files, 2001, The Cramer Company and Douglas Cramer, Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 10-11)
  - Client Files, 2001, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 12-13)
  - Client Files, 2001, Dedalus Foundation, Inc. (Robert Motherwell), Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 14-16)
  - Client Files, 2001, Willem de Kooning, Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 17-19)
  - Client Files, 2001, E, Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 2001, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2001, Richard Fisher and Jeannie Donovan, Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 2001, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 2001, Anthony Grant and Jonathan Seelig (Richard Serra), 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 2001, Kathy Grove and Larry List, 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2001, H, 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 26-28)
  - Client Files, 2001, J, 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Client Files, 2001, K, 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Client Files, 2001, Knoedler and Company, 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Client Files, 2001, L, 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 32-33)
  - Client Files, 2001, Lot 61, 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Client Files, 2001, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 1-3)
  - Client Files, 2001, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2001, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 5-6)
  - Client Files, 2001, Paine Webber, Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 7-8)
  - Client Files, 2001, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 9-10)
  - Client Files, 2001, Robert Rauschenberg, Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Client Files, 2001, Ted and Betsy Rogers (Jane Freilicher), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 2001, Judith Rothschild Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 13-17)
  - Client Files, 2001, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 18-20)
  - Client Files, 2001, S.C.S. Communications, Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2001, Thomas Segal Gallery (Paul Cézanne), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 22-24)
  - Client Files, 2001, Richard Serra, Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 25-26)
  - Client Files, 2001, Tony Smith Estate and Matthew Marks Gallery (Tony Smith), Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 2001, Ann Snitow, Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Client Files, 2001, T, Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Client Files, 2001, T, Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2001, Tishman Speyer (Damien Hirst), Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 2001, U-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 2001, W-Y, Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2002, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
  - Client Files, 2002, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
  - Client Files, 2002, Craig Baker (Hughie O'Donoghue), Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 2002, Banana Republic (David Salle), Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 2002, Kyle Brooks and Elena del Rivero (Elena del Rivero), Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD). (Box 18, Folder 11-13)
  - Client Files, 2002, Trisha Brown, Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 2002, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 15-16)
  - Client Files, 2002, Christie's (Brice Marden), Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2002, Paula Cooper Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 18-19)
  - Client Files, 2002, The Cramer Company, Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 20-24)
  - Client Files, 2002, George Cranmer, Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2002, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 2002, Dedalus Foundation, Inc. (Robert Motherwell), 1999-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 27-29)
  - Client Files, 2002, Estate of Willem de Kooning, Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2002, Willem de Kooning Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 2002, E-F, Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 3-4)
  - Client Files, 2002, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
  - Client Files, 2002, Gray Design, Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 2002, H-I, Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 2002, Alison Hilding, 1990-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 2002, Jeffrey Hoffeld and Company, 1990-2002; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD). (Box 19, Folder 10-11)
  - Client Files, 2002, J, Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 2002, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Client Files, 2002, Knoedler and Company, Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 14-15)
  - Client Files, 2002, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 16-17)
  - Client Files, 2002, Estate of Roy Lichtenstein, Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 18-19)
  - Client Files, 2002, Roy Lichtenstein Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 2002, Locksley Shea (Donald Judd), Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2002, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 22-24)
  - Client Files, 2002, Matthew Marks Gallery (Paul Feeley), Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2002, Matthew Marks Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 26-27)
  - Client Files, 2002, Sean Mellyn and Aldrich Museum, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2002, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 2002, James Nares, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 2002, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2002, Paiconom Properties Nominee, Inc., Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD). (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
  - Client Files, 2002, P.S.1 Contemporary Art Center, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 2002, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 8-10)
  - Client Files, 2002, Robert Rauschenberg, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Client Files, 2002, Judith Rothschild Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 2002, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 13-14)
  - Client Files, 2002, Salander-O'Reilly Galleries, LLC, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2002, Richard Serra, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 16-17)
  - Client Files, 2002, Sperone Westwater, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 2002, Stedelijk Museum and Brice Marden, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 19-20)
  - Client Files, 2002, T, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2002, U-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 2002, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 23-24)
  - Client Files, 2002, Virginia Bagley Wright (Ellsworth Kelly), Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2002, Jonathan Zuhovitsky, Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 26-29)
  - Client Files, 2003, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
  - Client Files, 2003, American Express Co., Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 3-4)
  - Client Files, 2003, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 5-7)
  - Client Files, 2003, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 8-9)
  - Client Files, 2003, Paula Cooper Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 2003, The Cramer Company, Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 11-13)
  - Client Files, 2003, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 14-15)
  - Client Files, 2003, Willem de Kooning Foundation and Office of Willem de Kooning, Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2003, E, Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2003, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 18-20)
  - Client Files, 2003, Lisa Freed, Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 21-23)
  - Client Files, 2003, Glenn Fuhrman, Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 2003, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2003, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
  - Client Files, 2003, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 3-4)
  - Client Files, 2003, I-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2003, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 2003, Knoedler and Company, Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 7)